<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Particle Life</string>
    <string name="physics_info">Change global simulation parameters</string>
    <string name="randomise_label">Randomise</string>
    <string name="reset_label">Reset</string>
    <string name="friction_label">Friction</string>
    <string name="friction_description">The amount by which particles are slowed over time.</string>
    <string name="force_strength_label">Force strength</string>
    <string name="force_strength_description">Global multiplier for all repulsive and attractive forces.</string>
    <string name="force_range_label">Force distance</string>
    <string name="force_range_description">Global multiplier for the distance at which the repulsive and attractive forces act.</string>
    <string name="pressure_label">Pressure</string>
    <string name="pressure_description">Strength of repulsion when particles get too close.</string>
    <string name="time_step_label">Time step</string>
    <string name="time_step_description">Simulation time step multiplier. Lower values lead to higher fidelity but slower simulation, higher values lead to faster simulation with more instability.</string>
    <string name="particles_info">Modify particles, species, and how they interact. These settings only take effect upon generating new particles.</string>
    <string name="generate_new_particles_label">Generate Random Particles</string>
    <string name="number_of_particles_label">Number of particles</string>
    <string name="number_of_particles_description">Too many particles will impact simulation performance.</string>
    <string name="number_of_species_label">Number of species</string>
    <string name="number_of_species_description">More species increases the complexity.</string>
    <string name="force_value_range_label">Force value range</string>
    <string name="force_value_range_description">Maximum and minimum values for repulsion/attraction forces between species. Positive values indicate repulsion and negative values indicate attraction.</string>
    <string name="edit_force_values_label">Edit Current Force Values</string>
    <string name="edit_force_values_description">Tap a colour to view and edit that species\' interaction values with other species. Negative values indicate attraction, positive values indicate repulsion.</string>
    <string name="about_particle_simulation">A particle simulation, designed to illustrate life-like behaviour emerging from particles obeying a set of simple rules.</string>
    <string name="about_particle_force_explanation">Each particle exerts a force on other nearby particles, depending on their species (represented by the different colours). This can either be a repulsion or an attraction, and is not necessarily symmetric. For example, red can be attracted to green, but green could be repulsed by red, which would result in red \"chasing\" green.</string>
    <string name="about_particle_extras">To avoid particles speeding up forever, a global friction is applied that slows particles down. Additionally, all particles repel each other if they get too close for comfort, like a kind of degeneracy pressure</string>
    <string name="about_particle_final">Play around with different settings to discover which parameters result in the most \"life-like\" creatures.</string>
</resources>